Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - Extension. Johnson, Alvin A.; Durfee, Arthur E.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service; Grange League Federation; United Fund., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Extension Service, Other Counties., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Extension Service Plans of Work. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Annual 4-H Club Conference. Four-H Club; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Cornell University Board of Trustees "New York's Changing and Adjusting Agriculture". New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Agricultural and Professional Improvement Fund. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - County 4-H Agents., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Operation Advance, Stage II. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Agricultural Outlook., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Research Extension Project in Agronomy and Plant Breeding. Kennedy, W. Keith; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agronomy., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Extension, County Agricultural Agents. Cole, Ernest J.; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - A.A. Johnson. Johnson, Alvin A., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - "Telling Extension's Story." New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Campbell, Howard H. Gibbons, Eugene F.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - State Agricultural Leaders, Crowe etc. Swan, John C.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Industrial Extension Service. Farkas, Daniel F.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Faculty of the New York State College of Agriculture. Watkins, Thomas C., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Farm Management Survey. Alexander, Frank D., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Finance and Business Office. Walsh, Robert L.; Cornell University, Finance and Business Office., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Florist Course., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Food Research Committee. Hester, Elizabeth., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Foreign Correspondence. Rockcastle, Verne N.; Oman, Paul., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Foreicjn Students. Morris, Fred B., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Foreign Visitors Contact Office. Morris, Fred B.; Cornell University, Foreign Visitors Office., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Freshmen Convocation. MacCorkle, Emmett W., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Foundation Newsletter. Cornell University, Office of University Development., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Gifts, Unrestricted., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Gifts to the College of Agriculture. Mitchell, Albert K.; Miller, John I.; Kent, George C., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Gifts. Sawtell, Edward R.; Hertel, John P.; Dairy industry., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Graduate School. Cornell University, Graduate School., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Graduate School, Scholar Incentive Forms., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Graduates, September and February., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; New York State College of Home Economics., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Industrial Extension Proposal. Campbell, Ralph N.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Libraries, Space Requirements. Miller, J. Gormly., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Los Banos. Romulo, Carlos P.; Umali, D.L.; Turk, Kenneth L.; Univ. of the Philippines; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Marketing Seminar, College of Agriculture. Milk marketing., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Form., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Morrill Centennial Lectures. Nesius, Ernest J., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Myers, William I. Stephens, Tommy; Carson, Rachel., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Ornamentals Laboratory Fire. Seeley, John G., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Cornell Plantations. Rockwell, George H.; Seeley, John G.; Lewis, Richard M.; Wright, T.P.; Cornell Plantations; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Suzanne Property, Lake Placid. Uihlein, Henry; Suzanne, Jacques., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Poultry. Swan, John C., 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Resident Instruction, Dolliver Reports. Dolliver, James S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Grant for Plant Physiology. Rockefeller Foundation., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - J.J. Millman Promotion, Rural Education. Millman, J.J.; Stutz, Frederick H., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Russian Exchange Students. Flucher, George; Smekalov, Nikolai A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Committee on Soviet Studies., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Salary Schedules, Position Titles and Grades, N«w York State Colleges and Experiment cations., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Siegal, Harvey A.; Wickham, Donald J.; Murray, J. Lawrence; Catherwood, Martin P., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Student Faculty lunch, 24 May 1963., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Student Organizations Officers. Hertel, John P., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Television Project. Dillingham, Howard, Howard I.; Phillips, Elmer S.; Ward, William B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Debt. of Extension Teaching and Information., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Visual Arts. Philps, Elmer S., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Youth Programs, Natural Science, Agricultural Science. Lathwell, Douglas J., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - A Miscellaneous. Alc, Daniel G., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Agr D Adams, Morton., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Agricultural Research Institute. Kc nil it L j, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural Businessmen's Council Members. Kc nil it L j, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Education, National Seminar. National Center for Advanced Study and Research in Agricultural Education., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Agricultural Research Institute., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - American Agriculturist. Eastman, Edward R.; Ingalls, Irving W.; Weatherby, Jack R.; American Agriculturist Foundation., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural Leaders Forum, 21 March 1963, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - American Society of Agronomy Service Awards. Neely, J. Winston; American Society of Agronomy., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - American Bankers Association, Agricultural Credit and Related Data., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - B Miscellaneous. Barraclough, Solon L.; Beneway, Frank W.; Beach, Barthly; Buffalo Bill Historical Center., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Bankers School of Agriculture. New York State Bankers Association., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Barge Canal., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Bolivia Project. Inter-University Program., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Biology Program, Ford Grant. Boynton, Damon; Ford Foundation., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - C Miscellaneous. Conroy, John H.; Cohn, Herman M.; Cory, Ernest N., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Campbell Soup Company., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Carey, Daniel J. Mutual Federation of Independent Cooperatives., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Census., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Council of Churches. Conklin, Theodore L.; New York State Council of Churches., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Conn Farm. Dominick, Ben A.; Cohn Farm., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - D Miscellaneous. Dedrick, Gilman T., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Dairy Herd Improvement Association., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Drought. Pack, A. Boyd., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - E Miscellaneous. Eakins, Silas., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Empire State Potato Club., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Entomological Society of America. Hall, David G.; Steinhaus, Edward A.; Poos, Fred W., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Exploring Food Systems for the Future Conference., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - F Miscellaneous. Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers1 Bargaining Agency., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Faculties Association., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Atomic Fallout Training Contract. Civil defense., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Farm Credit Banks of Springfield. Cameron, Gordon; Doe, J. Roberts; United States Farm Credit Administration., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Farm Dinner, Syracuse Chamber of Commerce., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Farmers Production Credit Association of Western New York. Hughes, Howell., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Farmhouse Fraternity. Nodland, Truman., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - United States Food and Drug Administration., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Ford Foundation. Mellor, John W., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Ford Program in Biology. Pimentel, David; Ford Foundation., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Forestry Research Law., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Foreign Agriculture. Hearne, Cannon C.; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Foreign Agricultural Service., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Freeze Damage., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - G Miscellaneous. Glick, Ira; Goldman, Max., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Genesee Valley Regional Market Authority. King, Joseph P., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Grange League Federation. Fallon, Edmund H.; Milliman, Thomas E.; Carson, Rachel; Ranney, Warren A.; Perkins, James A.; McConnell, James A., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Grange League Federation Marketing Survey. Flumerfelt, R.R.; Grange League Federation., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Grange League Federation Profit Egg Plan. Grange League Federation., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Grange League Federation, Cornell Centennial. Bruska, Walter G., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Goodbody and Company., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Grape Industry, New York State. Grape industry., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Grapes. Fournier, Charles; Grape industry; Vinifera; Labrusca., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Grocery Manufacturers of America. Willis, Paul S., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - H Miscellaneous. Hammond, Donald W., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Hatch Research Fund., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - High School Natural Science Program. Lathwell, Douglas J.; Watkins, Thomas C., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Hotels., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - I Miscellaneous. Isely, Dwight., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Income Tax Deferment on Compensation., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - International Congress of Limnology., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - International Cooperation Administration. Middaugh, Wesley S.; Council for Educational Cooperation with Africa; Tanganyika Agricultural College; Africa., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - International Development Society., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - International Horticultural Congress. Tukey, Harold B., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - International Ornithological Congress. International Union for Applied Ornithology., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - J Miscellaneous. Jones, Charles Hill., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Javits, Jacob K., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - K Miscellaneous. Knapp, Halsey B.; Umali, D.L., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - L Miscellaneous. Lerch, Donald; Lykken, Louis., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Land Grant Centennial Convocation. Stout, Perry R., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Land Grant College Seminar., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Map on Agricultural Regions of New York State., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - McDonald Farms. Trimberger, George W.; McDonald Farms; J.M. McDonald Foundation., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Agricultural Board; Shell Chemical Company; Agricultural Research Institute; National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council., 1962 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Agricultural Board. National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Agricultural Board. National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - New York Arborists Association. Callaway, George H.; New York State Arborists Association; Dutch Elm Disease., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - New York Florists' Club., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - New York State Grange. Curtis, Russell., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - New York Forest Owners Association., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - New York's Changing and Adjusting Agriculture., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - New York State Vegetable Growers Association. Allen, Stuart A., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - New York State Retirement System., 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - New York State Atomic Research Authority. Nuclear fuel., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Pathfinders Fish and Game Club. Ash, F.C.; Luke, Philip., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Root Rot Position. Martinson, Charles A., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Rural Church Institute. New York State Council of Churches., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Comparative Salary Information., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Scholar Incentive Program., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - United States Fur Animal Experiment Station. Turk, Kenneth L., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Wheat Referendum., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Z Miscellaneous. Zwingle, J.L., 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - President-Elect Perkins. Perkins, James A., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - President's Office. Adams, Morton; Perkins, James A.; Malott, Deane W.; Eisenhower, Dwight D.; Gyrisco, George G., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - President's Presentation. Perkins, James A., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Report of the President. Perkins, James A., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Provost S.S. Atwood, Dale Corson. Canoyer, Helen G.; Corson, Dale R.; Atwood, Sanford S., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Vice-President of Research and Advanced Study. Rogers, Thomas R.; Long, Franklin A.; Kennedy, W. Keith., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Vice-President for Academic Affairs. Keast, William R.; International Committee on Nutrition for National Defense., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Vice-President in Charge of Development. Zwingle, J.L., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Confidential Notes. New York State College of Agriculture, President's Committee., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Office of the Dean, Circular Letters, etc. New York State College of Agriculture, President's Committee., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Dean, Personal. National Academy of Sciences., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Dean's List, Card, etc. Hertel, John P., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Academic Deans Meetings., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Controller A.H. Peterson. Peterson, Arthur H., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Registrar's Office. Williams, Herbert H., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Secretary. Baldwin, Frank C., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University Administrative Flow Chart., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Director of Admissions. Storandt, Robert W., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Admissions to Agriculture. Shoup, Charles A.; Tyler, Howard S., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Admissions Report. Cornell University, Office of Admissions., 1963 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Schneider, Linda. Van Lare, Frank E., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Agricultural Economics. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Jennejahn, Luther; Treman, Allan H.; Spencer, Leland; Lutz, Edward A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics; New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Agricultural Economics, Applicants. Brown, Earl H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Economics., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Agricultural Economics, Food Chains. Earle, Wendell G., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Agricultural Education. Cushman, Harold R.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Education., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Agricultural Engineering. French, Orval C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agricultural Engineering., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Agricultural Leaders Forum, 25 MAR 1964. Schacter, Leon B.; Kiplinger, Austin H.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Agronomy. Cline, Marlin G.; Brady, Nyle C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agronomy., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Agronomy Department, Administrative Procedures. Cline, Marlin G.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Agronomy., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Agronomy, Applications., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Alumni Association. Warren, Stanley W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Association Annual Luncheon., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Animal Husbandry. Loosli, John K.; Visek, Willard J., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Animal Husbandry, Applicants. Coppock, Carl E.; Loosli, John K.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Amimal Husbandry., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Animal Husbandry, Beef Cattle Division. Miller, John I.; New York Beef Cattlemen's Association., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Animal Husbandry, Headship. Loosli, John K.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Animal Husbandry., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Animal Husbandry, Re-location of Dairy and Beef Cattle Barns. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Animal Husbandry., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Appointment Titles., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Bailey Hortorium. Dress, William J.; Moore, Harold E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Bailey Hortorium; Botanical Congress., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Professor Barraclough. Barraclough, Solon L., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Biochemistry. Williams, Harold H.; Moore, Harold E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Biochemistry; New York State College of Agriculture, Wing Hall; International Congress of Nutrition., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Program in Biochemistry. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Biochemistry., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Biometrics. New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Plant Breeding., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Botany. Kent, George C.; Key, Joe L.; Gates, David M.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Botany., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Board of Trustees. Stamp, Neal R.; New York State College of Agriculture, Board of Trustees., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Budget., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Bond, Maurice C. Ford Foundation; New York State College of Agriculture, Los Banos Project., 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Budget Conferences with Department Heads., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Budget Seminars., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Buildings and Properties. Weinhold, Julius F., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Business and Finance Office. Kilby, Paul C; Walsh, Robert L.; Cornell University, Business and Finance Office., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Calendar of Events., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Center for International Studies. Muller, Steven; Cornell University, Center for International Studies., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Cornell Clinic., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Conservation. Swanson, Gustav A.; Hamilton, Lawrence S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Conservation; New York State College of Agriculture, Fernow Hall., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Conservation, Applicants. McNeil, Richard; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Conservation., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Cornell University Council., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Cornell University Council, Administrative Board. Collacott, Robert H.; Zwingle, J.L., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Agricultural College Council Meeting, 28 MAY 1964. New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Agricultural College Council, Letters Acknowledging Appointment. New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Cornell University Counsel, Stamp and Meigs. Cornell University, Office of the University Counsel., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Dairy and Food Science. Buck, Paul A.; Holland, Robert F.; Kosikowski, Frank V.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Dairy and Food Science., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Dairy Bar and Milk Plant., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Duck Research Laboratory. Bruckner, Jacob H.; Leary, John G.; Duck industry., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - School of Education. Stutz, Frederick H.; Cornell University, School of Education; Educational Placement Bureau., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Letters from Recipients of Education and Aariculture. Colman, Gould P.; Freeman, Orville L.; Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Educational, Vocational Guidance Office. Andrus, Howard G., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Elliott Visit. Elliott, Carl; Cornell University, Cornell Nutrition Conference., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Projected Graduate and Undergraduate Enrollment Figures for Fall of 1964. Quotas., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Entomology. Pimentel, David; Dewey, James E.; Brann, James L.; Dates, Carolyn; Naegele, John A.; Dyce, Elton J.; Morse, Roger A.; Muka, Arthur A.; Matthysse, John G.; Gyrisco, George G.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology and Limnology; Insecticides., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Entomology, Headship. Pimentel, David; Gyrisco, George G.; Moore, Steve; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology and Limnology., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Entomology, Professor Bradley's Eightieth Birthday. Pimentel, David; Bradley, James C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology and Limnology., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Equipment Purchasing for New Facilities. Payne, Bruce M., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Equipment Acquisitions. Cornell University, Finance and Business Office., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Cornell Experiment Station. Kennedy, W. Keith; Shaul, Max V.; Metz, Joseph F.; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Cornell Experiment Station. Metz, Joseph F.; Boucault, Marie-Therese; Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station., 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 86)